<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.krfb.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">КРФБ</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">KRFB</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">КРФБ</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">KRFB</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Krfb</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKrfbxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Krfb</name>
  <summary>Desktop sharing</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ast">Compartición d'escritoriu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Compartició de l'escriptori</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Compartició de l'escriptori</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Sdílení pracovní plochy</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Skrivebordsdeling</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Freigabe der Arbeitsfläche</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Κοινή χρήση επιφάνειας εργασίας</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Desktop sharing</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Compartir el escritorio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Partage de bureau</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Compartición do escritorio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Condivisione del desktop</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Bureaublad delen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Współdzielenie pulpitu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Partilha do ecrã</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Compartilhamento de tela</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Zdieľanie pracovnej plochy</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Souporaba namizja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Дељење површи</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-Latn">Deljenje površi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Дељење површи</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Deljenje površi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Skrivbordsdelning</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Masaüstü paylaşımı</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Спільне користування стільницею</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxDesktop sharingxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">桌面共享</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Krfb Desktop Sharing is a server application that allows you to share your current session with a user on another machine, who can use a VNC client to view or even control the desktop.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ast">Krfb ye una aplicación sirvidora que te permite  compartir la to sesión actual con un usuariu n'otra máquina que puea usar un veceru VNC pa ver o controlar l'escritoriu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Krfb és una aplicació de servidor que permet compartir la vostra sessió actual amb un usuari en una altra màquina, la qual pot emprar un client VNC per veure o controlar l'escriptori.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Krfb és una aplicació de servidor que permet compartir la vostra sessió actual amb un usuari en una altra màquina, la qual pot emprar un client VNC per veure o controlar l'escriptori.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Krfb-skrivebordsdeling er et serverprogram der giver dig mulighed for at dele din nuværende session med en bruger på en anden maskine som kan bruge en VNC-klient til at vise eller endda styrer skrivebordet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Krfb ist eine Serveranwendung, welche die gemeinsame Benutzung der aktuellen Sitzung mit einem Benutzer auf einem anderen Rechner ermöglicht, der mit Hilfe eines VNC-Programms den Bildschirminhalt sehen oder sogar die Arbeitsfläche bedienen kann.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Η κοινή χρήση επιφάνειας εργασίας Krfb είναι μια εφαρμογή εξυπηρετητή που σας επιτρέπει να μοιράζεστε την τρέχουσα συνεδρία σας με έναν χρήστη σε άλλο μηχάνημα, ο οποίος μπορεί να χρησιμοποιεί έναν πελάτη VNC για να παρακολουθεί ή και να ελέγχει την επιφάνεια εργασίας σας.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Krfb Desktop Sharing is a server application that allows you to share your current session with a user on another machine, who can use a VNC client to view or even control the desktop.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Krfb para compartir el escritorio es una aplicación de servidor que le permite compartir su sesión actual con un usuario de otra máquina, que puede usar un cliente VNC para ver e incluso controlar su escritorio.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le partage de bureau Krfb est une application de serveur qui vous permet de partager votre session courante avec un utilisateur sur une autre machine, qui peut utiliser un client VNC pour afficher et même contrôler le bureau.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Krfb é un aplicativo de servidor que permite compartir a sesión actual cun usuario que está noutro equipo, que pode usar un cliente VNC para ver ou mesmo controlar o escritorio.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Condivisione del desktop Krfb è un'applicazione server che permette di condividere la sessione attuale con un utente su un'altra macchina, che potrà usare un client VNC per visualizzare ed anche controllare il desktop.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Bureaublad delen is een server-applicatie die u in staat stelt uw huidige sessie te delen met een gebruiker op een andere machine, die een VNC-client kan gebruiken om uw bureaublad te bekijken of zelfs te besturen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Współdzielenie pulpitu Krfb jest aplikacją serwerową, która umożliwia współdzielenie twojej bieżącej sesji z użytkownikiem na innym komputerze, który może użyć klienta VNC do oglądania,a a nawet sterowania twoim pulpitem.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">A Partilha de Ecrã Krfb é uma aplicação de servidor que lhe permite partilhar a sua sessão actual com um utilizador noutra máquina, o qual poderá usar um cliente de VNC para ver ou mesmo controlar o ambiente de trabalho.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Krfb je serverová aplikácia, ktorá vám umožní zdieľať vaše aktuálne sedenie s používateľom na inom stroji, ktorý môže používať VNC klienta na pripojenie alebo ovládanie stanice.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Souporaba namizja Krfb je strežniški program, ki vam dovoli, da delite vašo trenutno sejo z uporabnikom na drugem računalniku, ki ima odjemalec VNC. Uporabnik lahko gleda ali celo nadzira namizje.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">КРФБ је серверски програм за дељење површи, којим можете да поделите своју текућу сесију са корисником на другој машини. Удаљени корисник може да употреби неки ВНЦ клијент за гледање површи, па чак и управљање њоме.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">KRFB je serverski program za deljenje površi, kojim možete da podelite svoju tekuću sesiju sa korisnikom na drugoj mašini. Udaljeni korisnik može da upotrebi neki VNC klijent za gledanje površi, pa čak i upravljanje njome.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">КРФБ је серверски програм за дељење површи, којим можете да поделите своју текућу сесију са корисником на другој машини. Удаљени корисник може да употреби неки ВНЦ клијент за гледање површи, па чак и управљање њоме.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">KRFB je serverski program za deljenje površi, kojim možete da podelite svoju tekuću sesiju sa korisnikom na drugoj mašini. Udaljeni korisnik može da upotrebi neki VNC klijent za gledanje površi, pa čak i upravljanje njome.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Krfb-skrivbordsdelning är ett serverprogram som gör det möjligt att dela aktuell session med en användare på en annan dator, som kan använda en VNC-klient för att betrakta eller till och med kontrollera skrivbordet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Krfb Masaüstü Paylaşımı, mevcut oturumu masaüstünü görüntülemek veya kontrol etmek için, VNC istemcisi kullanan başka bir makinedeki, kullanıcıyla paylaşmanızı sağlayan bir sunucu uygulamasıdır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Програма для спільного використання стільниці Krfb — це серверна програма, яка надає вам змогу розділити ваш поточний сеанс роботи з користувачем, який працює на іншому комп’ютері, так, щоб цей користувач зміг скористатися клієнтом VNC для перегляду або навіть керування вашою стільницею.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKrfb Desktop Sharing is a server application that allows you to share your current session with a user on another machine, who can use a VNC client to view or even control the desktop.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">Krfb 桌面共享是一个可以让您与另一个在其他机器上的用户共享当前会话的服务器程序，他可以使用 VNC 客户端来查看甚至控制桌面。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>
        https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/krfb/krfb.png
      </image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>krfb</binary>
  </provides>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
</component>
